(忆往昔)
萨姆 我们救了很多人 但救不了所有的人
Look, Sam. We save a lot of people, but we just can't save them all.
我叫梅格
I'm Meg.
罗纳德·雷斯尼克
Ronald Resnick.
这位是特别探员维克多·亨里克森
This is Special Agent Victor Henricksen.
迪恩，你不会下地狱的
dean,you're not gonna go to hell.
小可爱们 上吧
sic him,boy.
救救我啊
somebody help me!
干得漂亮 萨姆
getting pretty slick there,sam.
地狱究竟发生了什么 露比
what the hell is going on around here,ruby?
你是谁
who are you?
卡西迪奥
castiello.
我就是那个紧紧抓住你把你带离地狱的人
i'm the one who gripped you tight and raised you from perdition.
我的意思是你是什么
i mean  what  are you?
我是侍奉主的天使
i'm an angel of the lord.
为什么一个天使要救我出地狱呢？
why would an angel rescue me from hell?
因为这是上帝的命令
because god commanded it.
因为我们有任务要交给你
because we have work for you.
你好，我是奥利维亚 我现在不在家 请留言
hey,it's olivia.i'm not in. leave a message.
奥利维亚 我是鲍比
olivia,it's bobby.
听到留言之后 给我回个电话
call me back,would you?
我这有个大麻烦 我需要你的帮助
i got something big.i could use your help.
是你
you!
我很抱歉
i'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
i'm so sorry.
[邪恶力量 第4季第2集]
那好 你再告诉我还有什么其他的可能性
well,then tell me what else it could be.
你瞧 就我所知这世上根本就没有天使
look,all i know is i was not groped by an angel.
好吧 想想 迪恩
okay,look,dean.
你凭什么觉得这个卡西迪奥要对你说谎呢
why do you think this castiello would lie to you about it?
也许他就是某种恶魔 恶魔就会说谎
maybe he's some kind of demon. demons lie.
哪个恶魔会不怕盐圈和陷阱
a demon who's immune to salt rounds and devil's traps...
以及露比的刀
and ruby's knife?!
迪恩 就算是莉莉丝也害怕这些东西
dean,lilith is scared of that thing!
你不会想想如果那真的是天使
don't you think that if angels were real,
有哪个猎人在哪里
that some hunter somewhere
曾见到过一个天使 或是在哪一刻?
would have seen one... at some point...ever?!
当然 你就有啊 迪恩
yeah. you just did,dean.
我是试图提出这个理论
i'm trying to come up with a theory here.
明白吗 跟着我的思路
okay? work with me.
迪恩 这个理论已经存在
dean,we have a theory.
那好 那就麻烦不要再神化这件事了
yeah,one with a little less fairy dust on it,please.
好 听着 我不是说我们就确信了
okay,look. i'm not saying we know for sure.
我只是说我认为我们
i'm just saying that i think we...
好了 好了 这个就是关键点
okay,okay. that's the point.
我们不知道该确信什么 所以我根本就不想相信
we don't know for sure,so i'm not gonna believe
那是什么侍奉主的破天使
that this thing is a freaking angel of the lord
就因为他那样说
because it says so!
你们两个笨蛋是想继续为了宗教信仰吵个不停
you two chuckleheads want to keep arguing religion,
还是想到我这儿来看看这个?
or do you want to come take a look at this?
我找了大堆相关传说 圣经上的 非圣经上的
i got stacks of lore, biblical,pre-biblical.
还有那些该死的楔形文字的
some of it's in damn cuneiform.
所有的都说到了天使可以从地狱中拯救灵魂
it all says an angel can snatch a soul from the pit.
还有呢
what else?
还要有什么?
what else,what?
还有谁能做到做一点?
what else could do it?
你这是在钻牛角尖
airlift your ass out of the hot box?
我能告诉你的就这么多了
as far as i can tell,nothing.
迪恩 这是个好消息 怎么说?
dean,this is good news. how?
因为这一次是真的
because for once,
这次不再是恶魔的另一个谎言了
this isn't just another round of demon crap.
我的意思是 也许你已经被一个好人救了 你明白了？
i mean,maybe you were saved
那好 如果说这是真的 如果说世上真的有天使
okay. say it's true. say there are angels.
还有什么 世上真的有个上帝
then what? there's a god?
在这一点上 就像是在拉斯维加斯赌大小 信则灵
at this point,vegas money's on yeah.
我不知道了 伙计们
i don't know,guys.
好了 想想
okay,look.
我知道你不是一个信徒
i know you're not all choirboy about this stuff,
但这越来越多的事实成为了那一点点信仰的证据
but this is becoming less and less about faith
而证据却多了
and more and more about proof.
证据? 对
proof? yes.
证明这个世界上有一个上帝存在
proof that there's a god out there
而我却在这里胡扯?
that actually gives a crap about me personally?
很抱歉 我可不买他的账
i'm sorry,but i'm not buying it.
为什么不呢?
why not?
因为为什么会是我?
because why me?
如果真的有上帝在这 为什么他为什么要我在这里胡扯
if there is a god out there,why would he give a crap about me?!
- 迪恩 - 我的意思是 我也救了很多人 对吧
- Dean - I mean,i've saved some people,okay?
我想要弥补这种偷鸡摸狗的行为
i figured that made up for the stealing
但是为什么我能获得救赎 我是一个普通人
but why do i deserve to get saved? i'm just a regular guy.
很明显 你是个正常人
apparently,you're a regular guy
这点在你脑子里很重要
that's important to the man upstairs.
真他妈的麻烦
well,that creeps me out.
我可不喜欢一个人开生日派对
i mean,i don't like getting singled out at birthday parties,
和...上帝
much less by...god.
好吧 这有点麻烦 迪恩
okay,well,too bad,dean,
也许他要你戴好你的生日帽
because i think he wants you to strap on your party hat.
好吧 对天使我们知道多少?
all right. what do we know about angels?
开始看吧
start reading.
你去买点派给我
you're gonna get me some pie.
好的  迪恩 我得先取点钱
yes,dean,i'll get the chips.
伙计
dude.
什么时候我忘记过派?
when have i ever forgotten the pie?
没错
exactly.
我得走了
i got to go.
对 再见
yeah,all right. bye.
-露比 -这是真的吗?
ruby. so,is it true?
什么真的?
is what true?
天使救了迪恩?
did an angel rescue dean?
你听说了
you heard.
谁干的?
who hasn't?
还有100%确定 不过我认为是这样的
we're not 100% sure,but i think so.
好吧  再见  萨姆
Okay. bye,sam.
等等  怎么了
Whoa,whoa,whoa,whoa. wait. what's going on?
萨姆  他们可是天使  而我是恶魔
Sam,they're angels. I'm a demon.
他们可不在乎我是否是良民
They're not gonna care if I'm being helpful.
而是不分青红皂白的赶尽杀绝
They smite first,and then they ask questions later.
你还知道他们些什么
What do you know about them?
不多
Not much.
我从未遇到过  也不想遇到
I've never met one,and I don't really want to.
我所知道的是他们会吓破我的胆
All I know is that they scare the holy hell out of me.
你自己小心  萨姆
Watch yourself,sam.
我才不怕天使呢
I'm not scared of angels.
别关引擎
Keep the engine running.
为什么  怎么了
Why? what's going on?
我有个朋友在另一个州  奥利维亚·罗莉
I got a friend one state over, Olivia Lowry.
天使事件发生三天来我都试着和她联系
I've been trying to reach her for three days on this angel thing.
忽视了这么多个电话  这可不像她
It's not like her to ignore this many calls.
奥利维亚·罗莉  是一个猎鬼者吗
Olivia Lowry, a hunter,right?
是的  我们要去看看她  你也一起吧
Yeah. we're gonna go check on her. you guys follow me.
挪旁边点  好的
Scoot over. yeah.
伙计  怎么了
Dude? yeah?
派呢
Where's the pie?
奥利维亚
Olivia?
鲍比
Bobby?
盐条
Salt line.
奥利维亚当时正在调试EMF测鬼器
Olivia was rocking the emf meter.
有灵魂在活动
Spirit activity.
是啊  激素调节
Yeah, on steroids.
我从没见过鬼把人虐成这样的
I never seen a ghost do this to a person.
鲍比  你还好吗
Boy,you all right?
最近我打电话给了一些猎人们
I called some hunters nearby...
好极了  他们可以帮助我们
Good. we can use their help.
但他们都没接我电话
...except they ain't answering their phones either.
有事发生了是吧
Something's up,huh?
你觉得呢
You think?
我是杰德  现在不在  请留言
Yeah,this is jed. I'm not around. uh,leave a message.
杰德  还是迪恩·温彻斯特
Jed,dean winchester again.
鲍比·辛格的朋友
Friend of bobby singer's.
听着  我们觉得有事情发生了
Look,we think something's happening.
猎人们都出事了
We think it's happening to hunters.
只是想确保你没事  给我回个电话吧
Just want to make sure you're okay. call me back.
情况不妙
It's not pretty.
他看起来比奥利维亚更糟  你那儿怎样
He looks even worse than olivia. what about you?
我检查了卡尔·贝茨和R.C.亚当斯
I checked on carl bates and r.c. adams.
他们被面目全非后扔在了床上
They've redecorated... in red.
到底他妈的怎么回事  鲍比
What the hell is going on here,bobby?
为什么一群鬼
Why did a bunch of ghosts
突然想要扳倒猎鬼者呢
Suddenly want to gank off-duty hunters?
我不知道  但在我们所有发现之前
I don't know,but until we find out,
你们最好呆在我地方
You guys better get your asses to my place.
我们已经上路了
We're on our way.
你好  萨姆  好久不见
Hi,sam. it's been a while.
伙计  好久不见
Hi,guys. it's been a while.
所以  为什么我们没死
So,how do we survive?
亨里克森  你不是已经
Henriksen. Are you... Did you...
我没复活
I didn't survive...
如果你想问的是这个的话
If that's what you're asking.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道你很内疚
I know you are.
听着  如果我们知道莉莉丝会来
Look,if we'd known lilith was coming...
你绝不会让六个无辜的人
You wouldn't have left half a dozen innocent people
死在警察局  这只是你的立场
In that police station to die in your place.
但你却这么做了  这是你的错
You did this to me. it was your fault.
她是随你而来的  我为此付出了代价
She was after you,and I paid the price.
是你让我们留在那儿死去的
You left us there to die!
见鬼  鲍比  快接电话
Damn it,bobby! pick up!
你感觉怎样  看看这是几
How you feeling,huh? how many fingers am I holding up?
零  我很好  迪恩
None. I'll be fine,dean.
刚那是亨里克森吗  对
Henriksen? yep.
为什么  他想怎样
Why? what did he want?
因为我们害他被杀而来报仇
Revenge 'cause we got him killed.
萨姆  的确是我们害了他  迪恩
Sam. well,we did,dean.
好吧  别再讲了
All right. stop right there.
管他妈的到底发生了什么  现在应验在我们身上了
Whatever the hell is going on,it's happening to us now,okay?
我联系不上鲍比  所以如果你不是在想答案
I can't get ahold of bobby,so if you're not thinking answers,
就啥也别想了
Don't think at all.
鲍比
Bobby?
我继续在里面找  你去外面看看
I'll go. you check outside.
鲍比
Bobby?
Bobby?!
鲍比
Bobby?
出来  无论你是什么  快出来
Come out,come out,whoever you are.
迪恩·温彻斯特  还是这么专横
Dean winchester. still so bossy.
你不认识我了
You don't recognize me?
这才是我的原貌
This is what I looked like
是恶魔剪了我的头发
Before that demon cut off my hair
还穿的像个荡妇
And dressed me like a slut.
迪恩
Dean.
梅格
Meg?
你好
Hi.
没事
It's okay
我不是恶魔
I'm not demon
你是恶魔附身的女孩
You're the girl the demon possessed.
梅格·麦斯特
Meg masters.
很高兴最终能和你聊聊
Nice to finally talk to you
当我还没流血致死之时
When I'm not,you know,choking on my own blood.
没关系
It's okay.
说真的  我还是个高中生
Seriously,I'm just a college girl.
抱歉  曾经是
Sorry, was.
一天晚上我独自回家
I was walking home one night
就被那股黑烟附身了
And got jumped by all this smoke.
另一件你需要明白的事情就是  我是个囚犯
Next thing you know,I'm a prisoner...
在潜意识里是
In here.
当时  我是醒着的
Now,I was awake.
我不得不看着她杀死人类
I had to watch while she murdered people.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
是吗
Oh,yeah?
抱歉你把我扔出窗外
So sorry you had me thrown off a building.
- 我们想  - 不  你们没有想
- Well,we thought - No,you didn't think!
我一直在等  在祈祷
I kept waiting,praying!
我被困在里面  向你们呼救
I was trapped in there screaming at you!
请救救我
"just help me,please!"
你们不是帮助人类的吗  迪恩
You're supposed to help people,dean.
你们为什么不帮助我
Why didn't you help me?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
别再说抱歉了
Stop saying you're sorry!
梅格  梅格
Meg. meg...
我们不知道
We didn't know.
不
No...
你只知道毁灭
You just attacked.
你想过那个身体里还有个女孩吗
Did you ever think there was a girl in here?
没有
No.
你只是控制  杀戮然后烧光了
You just charged in,slashing and burning.
你认为你们是英雄吗
You think you're some kind of hero?
不  我不是
No,I don't.
你说的真对
You're damn right.
你有想过  被一个正统恶魔
Do you have any idea what it's like
折磨了几个月
To be ridden for months by pure evil...
而你的家人却束手无策的感受吗
...while your family has no idea what happened to you?
我们尽了最大努力了
We did the best we could.
你害怕吗  鲍比  我们害怕  鲍比
Are you scared,bobby? we were scared,bobby.
当魔鬼走向我们  把我们紧紧住住
When the monster came for us... and grabbed us tight.
我们连叫都叫不出来的时候  你却在旁边看着  鲍比
And we couldn't even scream. you were right there,bobby.
你就在房子里
You were in the house.
你离得那么近
You were so close.
鲍比
Bobby?!
你本可以救我们的  鲍比
You could have saved us nbobby.
我们来了  鲍比
We're here   bobby?!
你正好走过那扇门
You walked right past nthat door.
魔鬼抓住我们了  而你却没发现我们
The monster had us. Nand you didn't find us.
现在  他们也不会发现你了
And now nthey won't find you.
还不仅仅是我  迪恩  我有个妹妹
It wasn't just me   dean. Ni had a sister.
一个小妹妹  她很尊重我
A little sister. she worshiped me.
你知道有个小妹妹是什么感觉的  对吗
You know how nlittle siblings are   right?
他们能为你做任何事情
how they'll do anything for you.
我失踪以后她就跟以前不一样了
She was never the same nafter i disappeared.
她竟然
She just...
她竟然迷失了自己
She just got lost.
当看到我的尸体躺在太平间里
And when my body nwas lying in the morgue
- 被打得遍体鳞伤  支离破碎  - 梅格
Beat-up   broken... meg.
你知道她干什么了吗
...do you know nwhat that did to her?
她自杀了  都是因为你  迪恩
She killed herself! Nbecause of you   dean!
因为你想的都是你自己的家人
Because all you were thinking about was your family,
你的复仇  你的魔鬼们
Your revenge,and your demons!
你们再多说50个拉丁单词  我就能活下来了
50 words of latin a little sooner,and I'd still be alive.
我的小妹妹也能活下来了
My baby sister would still be alive.
这比血债得算在你头上  迪恩
That blood is on your hands,dean!
你说得对
You're right.
鲍比
Bobby!
坚持住  鲍比  我来了
Hold on,bobby! I'm coming!
鲍比
Bobby!
拜托  迪恩
Come on,dean.
你的脑子在地狱里被油炸了吗
Did your brain get french-fried in hell?
你用子弹可射不死我
You can't shoot me with bullets.
我不是射你
I'm not shooting you.
是铁灯架
Iron.
这么说来  他们都是我们认识的人了
So,they're all people we know?
不只是认识  还是些我们没救的人
Not just know. people we couldn't save.
对了  我在梅格身上看到点东西
Hey,I saw something on meg.
她活着的时候有刺青吗
Did she have a tattoo when she was alive?
我觉得没有
I don't think so.
她手上有个a-a标记  就象个图标
It was like a-a mark on her hand, almost like a brand.
- 我也看到过  在亨里克森身上  - 象什么
I saw a mark,too,on henriksen. what did it look like?
纸  谢谢
Uh,paper? thanks.
就是它
That's it.
我以前可能看到过
I may have seen this before.
我们得走了
We got to move. whoa.
- 跟着我  - 好  上哪里去
Follow me. okay. where are we going?
安全的地方  两个傻瓜
Some place safe,you idiot.
鲍比  这里是不是
Bobby,is this
实心铁墙  完全裹上了盐
Solid iron. completely coated in salt.
百分百防鬼
100% ghost-proof.
你铸造了个避难所?
You built a panic room?
我周末闲着没事嘛
I had a weekend off.
- 鲍比  - 怎么了
Bobby. what?
你真伟大
You're awesome.
这就是我不愿意追随上帝的原因
See,this is why I can't get behind god.
你想说什么
What are you talking about?
如果他不存在  也就算了  坏事总是发生在好人身上
If he doesn't exist,fine. bad crap happens to good people.
现实就是这样
That's how it is.
没有什么规律或原因  就是胡乱的  恐怖的魔鬼
There's no rhyme or reason, just random,horrible,evil...
我知道了  我能体会
I get it,okay. I can roll with that.
但是如果他不在  那他是干什么吃的
But if he is out there,what's wrong with him?
当所有这些好人正被撕成碎片的时候
Where the hell is he while all these decent people
上帝他爷爷的到底在哪里
Are getting torn to shreds?
死得就剩他一个了  他怎么活下去
How does he live with himself?
为什么他不出手帮忙
You know,why doesn't he help?
我没有用十英尺的杆子来碰这个
I ain't touching this one with at 10-foot pole.
对
Yeah.
- 找到了  -什么
Found it. what?
- 你看到的标记  在鬼身上的图标  - 怎么了
- The symbol you saw. - The brand on the ghosts... yeah?
魔印的证据
Mark of the witness.
证据? 什么证据?
Witness? witness to what?
不同寻常
The unnatural.
他们没一个是正常死亡
None of them died what you'd call ordinary deaths.
看那些鬼魂 它们被强制唤醒
See,these ghosts. They were forced to rise.
他们从痛苦中觉醒  更像是一群疯狗
They woke up in agony. they were like rabid dogs.
这不是它们的错
It ain't their fault.
-有人故意这么做的  -谁?
Someone rose them... on purpose. who?
我看上去像知道的人吗?
Do I look like I know?
但是那个家伙的法术是如此的强大
But whoever it was used a spell so powerful
在每一个灵魂上都烙上了印记
It left a mark,a brand on their souls.
不管是谁干的 这里面肯定有阴谋
Whoever did this had big plans.
叫做 魔印的召唤
It's called "the rising of the witnesses."
这就是古代的预言
It figures into an ancient prophecy.
等等
Wait,wait.
这预言是哪本书里的?
What... what book is that prophecy from?
是广泛出版的译本
Well,the widely distributed version's
给游客看的 你应该明白
Just for tourists,you know.
长话短说 这是个新发现
But long story short, revelations.
是个征兆 孩子们
This is a sign,boys.
什么征兆?
A sign of what? a sign of what?
天启
The apocalypse.
天启?
Apocalypse?
天启? 启示录?
The apocalypse,apocalypse?
四死亡骑士? 瘟疫?
The four horsemen,pestilence?
5美元一加仑的汽油?
$5-a-gallon-gas apocalypse?
其中之一
That's the one.
魔印的召唤是个里程碑
The rise of the witnesses is a mile marker.
好吧 那现在我们该干嘛?
Okay,so,what do we do now?
公路旅行
Road trip.
去体验下《大峡谷》 《星舰迷航》
Grand canyon,star trek experience.
兔八哥农场
Bunny ranch.
首先
First things first.
-去救下我们的朋友如何?-好吧
How about we survive our friends out there? great.
有没有什么办法在世界末日前离开这个鬼地方?
Any ideas aside from staying in this room until judgment day?
是一个符咒
It's a spell
能防止征兆的发生
To send the witnesses back to rest.
干不干?
Should work...
当然  这太棒了
Should. great.
如果我翻译的正确的话
...if I translate it correctly.
在这屋里有我们所需要的一切东西
I think I got everything we need here at the house.
你有机会搞到在这屋里的东西吗?
Any chance you got everything we need here in this room?
所以你突然觉得我们的好运
So,you thought our luck was gonna start now
现在才开始
All of a sudden?
符咒要围绕在明火旁边
Spell's got to be cast over an open fire.
书房的壁炉
The fireplace in the library.
正解
Bingo.
那不仅仅是个吸引人的
That's just not as appealing
避难所吧
As a ghost-proof panic room,you know?
互相掩护 给我瞄的准点
Cover each other. and aim careful.
在我完成之前不要把弹药耗完 否则等着它们撕碎你
Don't run out of ammo until I'm done,or they'll shred you.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
嗨 迪恩 还记得我吗?
Hey,dean. you remember me?
都给我趴下
Everybody on the floor now!
他有一双激光眼
He's got the laser eyes.
罗纳德  那个激光眼是吧
Ronald,huh? with the laser eyes?
我真希望对你说见到你真高兴
I wish I could say it's good to see you.
因为你 我死了
I am dead because of you.
而你应该是来帮我的
You were supposed to help me!
想开枪就开吧 别说话
If you're gonna shoot,shoot. don't talk.
去楼上的衣橱里把红色文件箱拿下来 挺沉的
Upstairs,linen closet, red hex box. it'll be heavy.
收到
Got it.
鲍比
Bobby.
在厨房抽屉里的餐具
Kitchen. cutlery drawer.
有个夹层
It's got a false bottom.
毒药 鸦片还有蒿草
Hemlock,opium,wormwood.
-鸦片? -快去
Opium? go!
鲍比
Bobby.
怪物吃掉我们的时候你就走在旁边
You walked right by us while that monster ate us all up.
你本可以救我们
You could have saved us.
你知道什么是离我远点吗 萨姆?
You know what really pisses me off,sam?
你看见这些个月我是怎么受苦的
You saw how I suffered for months.
我想你应该学会了很多东西
I thought you must have learned something.
我觉得我为了个所谓的东西而死
I thought I died for something.
梅格
Meg.
但是你和那个叫露比的恶魔在一起干什么
But what you're doing with that demon,ruby...
你知道多少清白的尸体被露比焚烧只为了寻求刺激?
How many innocent bodies has ruby burned through for kicks?
还有有多少女孩子像我?
How many girls just like me?
你却不把她送回地狱
And you don't send her back to hell?!
你是个怪物
You're a monster!
-迪恩? -鲍比我没事 快点继续
Dean? I'm all right,bobby! keep working!
维克多
Victor.
迪恩
Dean.
我懂
I know.
不 你不懂
No. you don't.
你的死是我的错
It's my fault you're dead.
我抛弃了你
I left you behind.
之后我就听到了爆炸声
And the minute I heard about that explosion,I thought,
我当时就应该明白
"i should have known."
我得保护你
I should have protected you.
哇哦 还不够快
Unh-unh. not so fast.
我觉得你的死和莉莉丝的到来
You think you left and lilith came
让我们都死在一片白光闪耀的爆炸中?
And we all died in a beautiful blast of...white light?
只要...
If only.
45分钟
45 minutes.
什么?
What?
超过45分钟
Over 45 minutes.
莉莉丝说她想找点乐子
Lilith said she wanted to have some fun.
先从你的知己开始
The secretary was first.
记得她么? 那个处女南茜
Remember her? nancy,the virgin.
莉莉斯把她的肉一片一片切下来
Lilith filleted nancy's skin off piece by piece
就在我们面前  让我们看着
Right in front of us,made us watch.
-南希一直在尖叫  -不
Nancy never stopped screaming. no.
就是这样的
That was the last.
维克多
Victor...
告诉我怎样才能公平
Tell me how it's fair.
有人把你从地狱里救出来  我却死了
You get saved from hell, I die.
凭什么你有机会重生  迪恩
Why do you deserve another chance,dean?
你还好吗?
You all right?
不太好
No.
走吧
Let's go.
罗纳德  老兄  我以为我们是朋友
Ronald. hey,come on,man. I thought we were pals.
我活着的时候是这样的
That's when I was breathing.
我现在想生吃了你
Now I'm gonna eat you alive.
表这样子  我又不是汉堡
Well...come on,I'm not a cheeseburger.
不!
No!
-萨姆!  -掩护鲍比!
-Sam!  -cover bobby!
鲍比!
Bobby!
迪恩!
Dean!
倒进壁炉!
Fireplace!
鲍比?
Bobby?
重要工作总是会有目击人的
Excellent job with the witnesses.
这些你都知道?
You were hip to all this?
我的确知道
I was,uh,made aware.
非常感谢这天使般的帮助
Well,thanks a lot for the angelic assistance.
你要知道  我心脏差点都没了
You know,I almost got my heart ripped out of my chest.
但是你还活得好好的
But you didn't.
我以为天使会像个监护人一样的
I thought angels were supposed to be guardians.
长着柔软的羽毛  戴着光环
Fluffy wings,halos...
就像迈克尔·兰登那样  不是个小混混
You know,michael landon. not dicks.
去读读圣经
Read the bible.
天使是上帝的战士  我是个士兵
Angels are warriors of god. I'm a soldier.
是吗?  那为什么你不战斗?
Yeah? then,why didn't you fight?
我来这里不是为了来保护你
I'm not here to perch on your shoulder.
我们有更重要的使命
We had larger concerns.
使命?
Concerns?
人们在这里被撕成碎片!
There were people getting torn to shreds down here!
还有  当这些惨剧发生的时候
And,by the way,while all this is going on,
上帝死哪去了  如果有上帝的话?
Where the hell is your boss,huh,if there is a god?
上帝的确存在
There's a god.
我不相信
I'm not convinced.
因为要是有上帝的话
'cause if there's a god.
那他妈的他到底在等什么?
What the hell is he waiting for,huh?
种族灭绝?  妖兽四起?
Genocide? monsters roaming the earth?
还是他妈的世界末日?
The freaking apocalypse?
在什么时候他会晃晃那该死的指头
At what point does he lift a damn finger
来帮助那些赖在这里的杂种们?
And help the poor bastards that are stuck down here?
-上帝在施行公义  -如果你说“是以神秘的方式进行“的话
-The lord works  -if you say "mysterious ways,"
我一定会揍死你的
so help me,I will kick your ass.
在有旁观者这件事上
So,bobby was right...
鲍比是对的
About the witnesses.
有一些...
This is some kind of a...
世界末日的征兆
Sign of the apocalypse.
这就是我们在这里的原因  要出大事了
That's why we're here. big things afoot.
是我想知道的事情吗?
Do I want to know what kind of things?
我相当怀疑  但是你需要知道
I sincerely doubt it,but you need to know.
那些复活的目击人是66封印之一
The rising of the witnesses is one of the 66 seals.
好吧  我想这该不是海洋世界里的节目吧
Okay. I'm guessing that's not a show at seaworld.
那些封印被莉莉丝给破坏了
Those seals are being broken by lilith.
她使了魔咒  她复活了那些目击人
She did the spell. she rose the witnesses.
不仅仅是这里
Mm-hmm. and not just here.
-其他20个猎人都死了  -当然
-20 other hunters are dead.  -of course.
她挑了那些猎鬼者救不了的受害者
She picked victims that the hunters couldn't save
所以他们能在我们周围出没
So that they would barrel right after us.
莉莉丝有她自己的幽默感
Lilith has a certain sense of humor.
那我们就消灭这些鬼魂
Well,we put those spirits back to rest.
这无关紧要  封印被破坏了
It doesn't matter. the seal was broken.
为什么一定要破坏那个封印?
Why break the seal anyway?
你可以把封印看作门上的锁
You think of the seals as locks on a door.
然后呢  最后一扇门打开了会...
Okay. last one opens and...
路西法就自由了
Lucifer walks free.
路西法?
Lucifer?
我以为路西法只是他们说的一个故事
But I thought lucifer was just a story they told
在恶魔主日学校里
At demon sunday school.
没有这种东西
There's no such thing.
3天以前  你还以为我不存在呢
Three days ago,you thought there was no such thing as me.
你想过为什么我们会跟你们合作吗?
Why do you think we're here walking among you now
这可是2000年以来的第一次
For the first time in 2,000 years?
为了阻止路西法
To stop lucifer.
这就是我们来这里的原因
That's why we've arrived.
以前的工作就到此为止了
Well... bang-up job so far.
现在的主要任务是那些目击人
Stellar work with the witnesses.
很好
That's nice.
我们试过了
We tried.
还有其他战斗  其他的封印
And there are other battles,other seals.
有些能赢  有些会输
Some we'll win,some we'll lose.
这次我们输了
This one we lost.
我们的人手是有限的
Our numbers are not unlimited.
这周我失去了6个弟兄
Six of my brothers died in the field this week.
你觉得天国的敌人们
You think the armies of heaven
只是为了攻击你吗?
Should just follow you around?
他们有更大的阴谋
There's a bigger picture here.
你应当对我尊重些
You should show me some respect.
我把你从地狱里拯救了出来
I dragged you out of hell.
也能再把你送回去
I can throw you back in.
你还好吗?
You all right?
怎么了  迪恩?
What's wrong,dean?
那么...
So...
你现在相信有
You got no problem believing in...
上帝和天使了吗?
God and angels?
不  还不太信
No,not really.
我猜这意味着你相信恶魔
So,I guess that means that you believe in the devil.
你为什么问我这些?
Why are you asking me all this?